A Guide to the Dudley S. Ingraham Papers 1980.0036
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series I: Correspondence, undated, 1901-1984
  - August - September, 1972 (Box 41:523)
  - October, 1972 (Box 41:524)
  - November, 1972 (Box 41:525)
  - December, 1972 (Box 42:526)
  - Janaury - March, 1973 (Box 42:527)
  - April - May, 1973 (Box 42:528)
  - June, 1973 (Box 42:529)
  - July - August, 1973 (Box 42:530)
  - September - october, 1973 (Box 42:531)
  - November - December, 1973 (Box 42:532)
  - January - February, 1974 (Box 42:533)
  - March, 1974 (Box 42:534)
  - April - May, 1974 (Box 42:535)
  - June, 1974 (Box 42:536)
  - July - August, 1974 (Box 42:537)
  - September, 1974 (Box 42:538)
  - October, 1974 (Box 42:539)
  - November, 1974 (Box 43:540)
  - December, 1974 (Box 43:541)
  - January, 1975 (Box 43:542)
  - February, 1975 (Box 43:543)
  - March - April, 1975 (Box 43:544)
  - May, 1975 (Box 43:545)
  - June - July, 1975 (Box 43:546)
  - August - September, 1975 (Box 43:547)
  - October, 1975 (Box 43:548)
  - November - December, 1975 (Box 43:549)
  - January - March, 1976 (Box 43:550)
  - April, 1976 (Box 43:551)
  - May - June, 1976 (Box 43:552)
  - July - August, 1976 (Box 44:553)
  - September, 1976 (Box 44:554)
  - October, 1976 (Box 44:555)
  - November - December, 1976 (Box 44:556)
  - Seymour, Kay, ca. 1975-1976 (Box 44:557)
  - January - June, 1977 (Box 44:558)
  - July - December, 1977 (Box 44:559)
  - Jaunary - June, 1978 (Box 44:560)
  - July - December, 1978 (Box 44:561)
  - 1979-1984 (Box 44:562)
- Series II: Personal Papers, undated, 1849-1976
  - Address book, pre 1958 (Box 44:563)
  - Art and Jewelry appraisals, 1962 (Box 51:685)
  - Artwork inventory, 1957 (Box 51:673)
  - Awards and citations, undated (Box 45:564, Folder OS)
  - Bradley, Warren J. diary, 1866 (Box 45:565)
  - Commissions, Boards, Councils and Organizations
    - Arts, 1920-1949 (Box 45:566)
    - Board of Fire Commissioners, 1947 (Box 45:567)
    - Boy Scouts of America award, 1941 (Box 51:687)
    - Boy Scouts of America plaque, 1976 (Box 51)
    - Bristol Clock Museum, undated, 1937 (Box 51:688)
    - Bristol Congregational Church, 1925-1928 (Box 45:568)
    - Bristol Rotary Club, 1938 (Box 45:569)
    - Chinese Leadership Fund, 1925-1926 (Box 45:570)
    - Corporate organizations, 1937-1938, 1958 (Box 45:571)
    - Foxhollow School
      - Board of Trustees minutes, 1961-1970 (Box 45:572)
      - Board of Trustees minutes, 1971-1977 (Box 45:573)
      - Development program, 1967-1969 (Box 45:574)
    - Georgica Association newspaper clippings, undated, ca. 1955-1965 (Box 51:674)
    - Highway Safety Commission, 1938-1941 (Box 45:575)
    - Membership organizations, 1922-1958 (Box 45:576)
    - School Board minutes, 1923-1926 (Box 45:577)
    - Union League of America (Mark Howard Correspondence), 1852-1864 (Box 45:578)
    - Union League of America, 1857-1865 (Box 45:579)
  - Family history, undated (Box 45:580)
  - Ingraham, Andrew, 1849-1851 (Box 45:581)
  - Ingraham Art Collection, 1933-1976 (Box 45:582)
  - Ingraham, Dudley, Jr., 1945-1953 (Box 45:583)
  - Ingraham, Grace, undated (Box 46:584)
  - Ingraham, Helga Estate, 1971-1977 (Box 46:585)
  - Ingraham House, 1920, 1965-1966 (Box 46:586)
  - Ingraham House drawing, undated (Box 51:686)
  - Ingraham, Robert A., 1953-1955 (Box 46:587)
  - Insurance and Securities, 1920-1966 (Box 46:588)
  - Investment Records, 1927-1929 (Box 46:589)
  - Invitations, 1937-1941 (Box 46:590)
  - Land Deeds, 1929-1964 (Box 46:591)
  - Memoranda, undated (Box 46:592)
  - Natural history information cards, undated (Box 51)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1926-1957 (Box 46:593)
  - Official documents, 1890-1976 (Box 46:594)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 46:595)
  - Property--Wainscott, Long Island (NY), 1925-1955 (Box 46:596)
  - Property--Wainscott, Long Island (NY), undated (Folder OS)
    Scope and Contents
    Blueprints and drawings
  - Speeches, 1935-1975 (Box 46:597)
  - Speeches--Notes on, 1930-1935 (Box 46:598)
  - Trust Deeds, 1931-1976 (Box 46:599)
  - Trust Estates, undated (Box 52:675)
  - Will--Ingraham, Dudley, 1975 (Box 47:600)
  - Will--Ingraham, Marion, 1934 (Box 47:601)
- Series III: Company records, 1921-1964
  - Advertisements and catalogs, 1927-1960 (Box 47:602)
  - Black Bill (30 hour week)--Correspondence, 1933-1935 (Box 47:603)
  - Bylaws and Stockholders meetings, 1953-1958 (Box 47:604)
  - Case Division Progress report, 1944 May (Box 47:605)
  - Clock Club, 1927-1938 (Box 47:606)
  - Clocks and Watches--Illustrations and blueprints, 1921-1925 (Box 47:607)
  - Clock Industry history--Writings and reminiscences, 1936-1962 (Box 47:608)
  - Company history--notes, 1962-1964 (Box 47:609)
  - Employee relations, 1928-1957 (Box 47:610)
  - Factory operating hours, 1933 (Box 47:611)
  - Financial records, 1922-1958 (Box 47:612)
  - Financial reports
    - 1962 (Box 52:676)
    - 1963 (Box 52:677)
    - 1964 (Box 52:678)
    - 1965 (Box 52:679)
    - 1966 (Box 52:680)
    - 1967 (Box 52:681)
  - Financial statements, 1964-1965 (Box 52:682)
  - Ingraham, Edward--Correspondence, 1947-1963 (Box 47:613)
  - Manufacturers Association of Hartford County, Inc., 1957-1961 (Box 47:614)
  - Memoranda, 1927-1962 (Box 47:615)
  - Notices posted, 1930-1951 (Box 47:616)
  - Mussey, Barrows, Young Father Time: A Yankee Portrait, 1948 April (Box 48:617)
  - P. R. Mallory & Company possible merger, undated (Box 51:689)
  - Product Class Sales in Pieces, 1951-1965 (Box 52:683)
  - Projections, 1964-1965 (Box 52:684)
  - Reports and minutes, 1934-1958 (Box 48:618)
  - Report on Radium poisoning, 1928-1935 (Box 48:619)
- Series IV: Anna Ingraham estate, 1920-1957
  - Accounts, 1920 (Box 48, Folder 620)
  - February - December, 1939 (Box 48, Folder 621)
  - March - April, 1940 (Box 48:622)
  - May - June, 1940 (Box 48:623)
  - July - December, 1940 (Box 48:624)
  - January - May, 1941 (Box 48:625)
  - June - September, 1941 (Box 48:626)
  - October - December, 1941 (Box 48:627)
  - January - August, 1942 (Box 48:628)
  - September 1942 - December 1943 (Box 48:629)
  - January 1945 - February 1946 (Box 48:630)
  - March - May, 1946 (Box 49, Folder 631)
  - June - September, 1946 (Box 49, Folder 632)
  - October - December, 1946 (Box 49:633)
  - January - February, 1947 (Box 49:634)
  - March, 1947 (Box 49:635)
  - April, 1947 (Box 49:636)
  - May, 1947 (Box 49:637)
  - June - July, 1947 (Box 49:638)
  - August - September, 1947 (Box 49:639)
  - October, 1947 (Box 49:640)
  - November - December, 1947 (Box 49:641)
  - January, 1948 (Box 49:642)
  - February, 1948 (Box 49:643)
  - March, 1948 (Box 50, Folder 644)
  - April, 1948 (Box 50, Folder 645)
  - May, 1948 (Box 50:646)
  - June, 1948 (Box 50:647)
  - July, 1948 (Box 50:648)
  - August, 1948 (Box 50:649)
  - September, 1948 (Box 50:650)
  - October - November, 1948 (Box 50:651)
  - January - March, 1949 (Box 50:652)
  - April, 1949 (Box 50:653)
  - May - June, 1949 (Box 50:654)
  - July - August, 1949 (Box 50:655)
  - September, 1949 (Box 50:656)
  - December, 1949 (Box 50:657)
  - January, 1950 (Box 50:658)
  - March - June, 1950 (Box 50:659)
  - July - December, 1950 (Box 50:660)
  - January, 1951 (Box 50:661)
  - April - June, 1951 (Box 50:662)
  - August, 1951 (Box 50:663)
  - March - December, 1952 (Box 50:664)
  - February, 1953 (Box 50:665)
  - April - May, 1953 (Box 50:666)
  - December, 1953 (Box 50:667)
  - January - March, 1954 (Box 50:668)
  - 1954 November - December (Box 50, Folder 669)
  - 1955 (Box 50, Folder 670f)
  - 1956 (Box 50, Folder 671)
  - 1957 January (Box 50, Folder 672)
- Series V: Inventory of additions, undated, 1926-1978
  - Correspondence, financial records, legal documents, 1926-1978 (Box 53)
    Scope and Content Note
    Financial records -Ingraham's lift insurance, retirement annuity and settlement proceeds -appraisal on Ingraham Furnishings in Bristol Connecticut (1932) -appraisal on Ingraham Furnishings in Bristol Connecticut (1935) -rugs appraisals (1931) -East hampton town tabular statement for tax roll of 1951-2 -tax receipt 1946-7 from town clerk of East Hampton, NY
    Legal documents -Last Will and Testament of George Dudley Seymouor (1943)
    Correspondence (letters) - from Samuel Donchian Rug company on rugs purchased -from Ingraham to Ivan Blish on getting in touch with Caroline Blish for "The Helmet Crab" painting